(Amy:)Sheldon, it's a beautiful night.
(Amy:)Why don't you and I
go for a nice walk together?
(Sheldon:)Oh, everything is just
sex with you isn't it?
(Raj:)Sheldon, I think
you might find the support
(Raj:)you're looking for, if you realize
(Raj:)that relationships
are a give and take.
(Raj:)She can only be there for you
(Raj:)as much as you are for her.
(Amy:)Thank you, Rajesh.
(Raj:)And, Amy, you need
to be patient with Sheldon,
(Raj:)instead of pressuring him
to accept intimacy on your terms.
(Sheldon:)You should probably go.
(Ira Flatow:)I'm Ira Flatow,
and this is Science Friday.
(Ira:)I'd like to welcome back
Dr. Sheldon Cooper,
(Ira:)who thought
he had discovered
(Ira:)a new super-heavy element
only to have it disproved
(Ira:)by my next guest,
Dr. Leonard Hofstadter.
Welcome to Science Friday,
gentlemen.
(Leonard:)-Thanks.
-Thank you.
(Sheldon:)Ira, if I may, I'd like to apologize
for my behavior last week.
(Ira:)It's all right.
(Sheldon:)Now, isn't there something
you'd like to say to me?